(Leonard:)He's in critical condition.
(Raj:)Oh, no!
(Bernadette:)Did you hear?
(Bernadette:)Isn't it terrible?
(Leonard:)Have you seen him?
(Bernadette:)They wouldn't let me in.
(Bernadette:)Oh, my Howie.
(Leonard:)It'll be okay.
It'll be okay.
(Leonard:)It'll be
okay.
(Raj:)It's Howard.
(Raj:)Howard, hello.
(Howard:)Raj, is that you?
(Raj:)Yeah, I'm right here,
buddy. How are you?
(Howard:)Shh, shh. Listen to me.
(Howard:)I'm not gonna make it.
(Raj:)No, no, no,
don't say that.
(Howard:)You're going to
be all right.
(Howard:)Raj, I don't have time.
Now, pay attention.
(Howard:)My last wish is that
you look after Bernadette.
(Raj:)Of course, of course.
Now when you say "look
after," you mean...
(Bernadette:)Sexually.
(Raj:)Excuse me, Bernadette.
I have to hear it from him.